[
    {
        "question": "What colour was Mr Blobby?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Blue and orange",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Purple and blue",
        "correct_ans": "Pink and yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which boyband did Robbie Williams belong to?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Spice girls",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Backstreet boys",
        "correct_ans": "Take that"
    },
    {
        "question": "ED how big dose mountains u climb?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "v173",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "v12",
        "correct_ans": "Itsy bitsy teenie weenie yellow polka dot bikini"
    },
    {
        "question": "How old was the oldest Tamagotchi when it died?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "219,792,099E156 tamayears",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "17 tamayears",
        "correct_ans": "145 tamayears"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour were the origional Pokemon games in the UK?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Gold & Silver",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Yellow",
        "correct_ans": "Red and blue"
    },  
    {
        "question": "How many original Pokemon were there?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "161",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "149",
        "correct_ans": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you proud of stealing?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Yes I am immoral",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "I didn't know I was stealing",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Japanese heritage mean nothing to you?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Yes, I love sushi",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "No, gimme my sword",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you a cop? You have to tell me if you're a cop.",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "No",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "No, really I'm not",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Would you steal a car?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Would you steal a television?",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Would you steal a handbag?",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who quit the band Busted first?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "James",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Matt",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Issy Young or Yeung?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "YUNG",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "YOURNG",
        "correct_ans": "Shut up Adam!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Should Ed get a coffee",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Yeah baby girl, you go",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Tea plz, no sugar, sweetie pie",
        "correct_ans": "Can I be the milk to your shake?"
    },
    {
        "question": "ED how big dose mountains u climb?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "v173",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Itsy bitsy teenie 5'10'' weenie yellow polka dot Ed",
        "correct_ans": "Itsy bitsy teenie weenie yellow polka dot bikini"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you hurt yourself falling from the vending machine, Adam?",
        "incorrect_ans_one": "Yes, I did, why?",
        "incorrect_ans_two": "Cuz u snack, shawty",
        "correct_ans": "Love to see what components are hiding in your wrapper"
    }
]